They were "Strange Fruit". Some called them the greatest rock band of the '70s. They haven't
played together for 20 years. No wonder they're worried about their performance.
Still Crazy is a comedy, music film directed by Brian Gibson.
In the 1970s, Strange Fruit were it.
They lived the rock lifestyle to the max, groupies, drugs, internal
tension and an ex front man dead from an overdose.
Even their demise was glamorous; when lightning struck
the stage during an outdoor festival.
Twenty years on, these former rock gods they have now sunk deep into obscurity when the idea of a
reunion tour is lodged in the head of Tony, former keyboard player of the Fruits.
Tony sets out to find his former bandmates with the help of former manager Karen to see
if they can recapture the magic and give themselves a second chance.
Tony Costello, played by Stephen Rea.
Hughie, played by Billy Connolly.
Les Wickes, played by Jimmy Nail.
David "Beano" Baggot, played by Timothy Spall.
Ray Simms, played by Bill Nighy.
Karen Knowles, played by Juliet Aubrey.
Still Crazy is a 1998 British comedy film directed by Brian
Gibson (his final film before his death in 2004).
The plot concerns a fictional 1970s rock band named Strange Fruit, who,  two decades after splitting up, are persuaded
to get back together to perform at a reunion in the same concert venue where they played their last gig.
The film focuses on the personal lives of the band members and those closest to them, their
individual experiences with approaching middle-age and the success that eluded them.
It was nominated for two Golden Globes in 1999 in two categories: Best
Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy and Best Original Song.
The film explores themes of manager, birthday, 1970s, bus, stage.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.